theweddingplan.in 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy - TheWeddingPlan

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their Personally identifiable information(PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.  

 **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.

 **When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

 **How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

 **How do we protect visitor information?**

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.

We do not use Malware Scanning.

We do not use an SSL certificate

  * We do not need an SSL because:

We are an Indian wedding planning portal & list wedding service providers details on our website. We ask for particulars of vendor and post the same on our website, however we put up only those details which have been publicize by the vendor himself/herself that too with their permission and confirmation through phone and in person. This is done only for business enhancement. Other than this we do not share the clients (those who are getting married) information publicly thus securing the vital data of the clients. Thus our process is solely for customer service and do not hamper on the personal security of the client or the vendor.

 **Do we use cookies?**

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

However, you can still place orders .

 **Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Google**

Google advertising requirements can be summed up by Googles Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google uses of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  

**We have implemented the following:**

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting   

  * DoubleClick Platform Integration

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website. 

Opting out:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

 **How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. 

**Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?**

It is also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

 **To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:**

 **  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at**

and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.  

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Last Edited on 2015-07-13
